What is Bitcoin?
Bitcoinとは?
Bitcoin is the first
Bitcoinは初めての
decentralized digital currency.
デジタル通貨です。
Bitcoins are digital coins
Bitcoinはインターネットを通し
you can send through the Internet.
送信できる デジタルコインです。
Compared to other alternatives,
他の代替通貨に比べて、
Bitcoins have a number of advantages.
Bitcoinにはいくつかの 利点があります。
Bitcoins are transferred
Bitcoinはインターネットを通じ
directly from person
個人同士で
to person
直接取引
via the net
でき、
without going through a bank
銀行や手形交換所を
or clearinghouse.
通す必要もありません。
This means that the fees are much lower,
これにより手数料が非常に 低く抑えられ、
you can use them in every country,
どの国でも使用でき、
your account cannot be frozen
口座を凍結される 心配もありません。
and there are no prerequisites
使用においての 必須条件や
or arbitrary limits.
制限もありません。
Let's look at how it works!
ではどのような仕組みか見てみましょう！
Bitcoins are generated all over the Internet
Bitcoinはインターネット上の あらゆる場所で
by anybody running a free application
Bitcoinを採掘できる 無料のアプリケーションを 使用しているすべてのユーザーによって
called a Bitcoin miner.
生成されています
Mining requires a certain amount of work
各ブロックのコインを採掘するには
for each block of coins.
それなりの作業量が必要です。
This amount is automatically adjusted
この作業量は自動的に
by the network
ネットワークにより調整されています
such that Bitcoins are always created
これによりBitcoinは常に 一定で
at a predictable and limited rate.
適切な量が生成されます。
Your Bitcoins are stored in your digital wallet
あなたのBitcoinは オンライン銀行口座のような
which might look familiar if you use online banking.
デジタル財布に蓄えられます。
When you transfer Bitcoins,
Bitcoinを送信すると
an electronic signature is added.
電子署名が添付されます。
After a few minutes
数分後
the transaction is verified by a miner
Bitcoin 採掘アプリケーションによって 取引が認証されます。
and permanently and anonymously stored
そしてネットワークに 匿名で永久に
in the network.
保存されます。
The Bitcoin software is completely open source
Bitcoinソフトウェアは オープンソースのため
and anybody can review the code.
だれでもコードを 見ることができます。
Bitcoin is changing finance
Bitcoinはネットが書物の発行を 変えたように
the same way the web changed publishing.
金融も変えています。
When everyone has access
多くの人がアクセスできる
to a global market,
グローバル市場では、
great ideas flourish.
様々な良質なアイディアが発展します。
Let's look at some examples
ではBitcoinがどのように 使用されているか
of how Bitcoins are already used today:
いくつかの例を 見てみましょう
You can purchase video games,
ゲームを購入したり、
gifts,
プレゼント、
books,
本、
servers
サーバー、
and alpaca socks.
アルパカ用の靴下だって。
Several currency exchanges exist
Bitcoinにはいくつかの
where you can trade your Bitcoins
通貨へ変換できます。
for dollars,
ドル、
euros
ユーロ、
and more.
他にもいろいろあります。
Bitcoins are a great way
Bitcoinは
for small businesses and freelancers
小規模ビジネスやフリーランスなどに
to get noticed.
注目されるのに最適です。
It doesn't cost anything to start accepting them,
Bitcoinを受け付けるのに 費用はかかりません、
there are no chargebacks or fees
引き落としや費用はなく
and you'll get additional business
Bitcoin経済により
from the Bitcoin economy.
新たなビジネスを得られます。
For your first Bitcoins and more information, visit:
Bitcoinに関する情報はこちら
weusecoins.com
weusecoins.com